prince2 = [
  {"question":"泛着淚光","Answer":"fànzhe lèiguāng"},
  {"question":"順着","Answer":"shùnzhe"},
  {"question":"臉頰","Answer":"liǎnjiá"},
  {"question":"滑落","Answer":"huáluò"},
  {"question":"平復","Answer":"píng fù"},
  {"question":"向","Answer":"xiàng"},
  {"question":"述說","Answer":"shù shuō"},
  {"question":"悲傷","Answer":"bēishāng"},
  {"question":"融洽","Answer":"róngqià"},
  {"question":"臣僕","Answer":"chénpú"},
  {"question":"靜默","Answer":"jìngmò"},
  {"question":"片刻","Answer":"piànkè"},
  {"question":"雖然","Answer":"suīrán"},
  {"question":"鉛","Answer":"qiān"},
  {"question":"凝視","Answer":"níngshì"},
  {"question":"表露","Answer":"biǎolù"},
  {"question":"真誠","Answer":"zhēn chéng"},
  {"question":"神情","Answer":"shénqíng"},
  {"question":"狹窄","Answer":"xiázhǎi"},
  {"question":"一楝","Answer":"yī liàn"},
  {"question":"破舊","Answer":"pòjiù"},
  {"question":"窗戶","Answer":"chuānghù"},
  {"question":"婦人","Answer":"fùrén"},
  {"question":"縫紉","Answer":"féngrèn"},
  {"question":"累得","Answer":"lěi dé"},
  {"question":"痠痛","Answer":"suāntòng"},
  {"question":"痕跡","Answer":"hénjì"},
  {"question":"顯得","Answer":"xiǎnde"},
  {"question":"粗糙","Answer":"cūcāo"},
  {"question":"嚷著","Answer":"rǎng zhe"},
  {"question":"橘子","Answer":"júzi"},
  {"question":"摘下","Answer":"zhāixià"},
  {"question":"劍柄","Answer":"jiàn bǐng"},
  {"question":"動彈","Answer":"dòngtan"},
  {"question":"沉思","Answer":"chénsī"},
  {"question":"伙伴","Answer":"huǒbàn"},
  {"question":"尼羅河","Answer":"níluóhé"},
  {"question":"楚楚可憐","Answer":"chǔchǔ kělián"},
  {"question":"實在","Answer":"shízài"},
  {"question":"不禁","Answer":"bùjīn"},
  {"question":"萌生","Answer":"méngshēng"},
  {"question":"念頭","Answer":"niàntou"},
  {"question":"摘下","Answer":"zhāixià"},
  {"question":"銜著","Answer":"xiánzhe"},
  {"question":"奮力","Answer":"fènlì"},
  {"question":"振翅","Answer":"zhènchì"},
  {"question":"翻來覆去","Answer":"fānlái fùqù"},
  {"question":"疲倦","Answer":"píjuàn"},
  {"question":"沈沈","Answer":"shěnshěn"},
  {"question":"呼嘯","Answer":"hūxiào"},
  {"question":"揮動","Answer":"huīdòng"},
  {"question":"涼爽","Answer":"liángshuǎng"}
  ]